

# JOHN MATTHEW T. GERNALE

- ☐ 09858648265 matthewgernale26@gmail.com
- Block 54 Lot 8 Sonoma Residences, Sta. Cruz, Santa Maria, Bulacan 3022

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a recent Computer Engineering graduate from Polytechnic University of the Philippines and a Civil Service Exam Professional pass holder. My expertise lies in web development and embedded system engineering, complemented by a strong understanding of computer hardware and software. In addition to my technical skills, I have a creative side, with freelancing experience in graphic design, layout design, and photo editing using Adobe Photoshop.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# INTERNSHIP Pru Life UK, Pasig City

08/2022 - 09/2022

- Web Developer and Graphic Designer with experience in Social Media Management at Pru Life UK.
- Integral part of a dynamic team responsible for creating engaging digital experiences.
- Proficient in web development, graphic design, and overseeing the company's Facebook presence.
- Thrived in a fast-paced, collaborative environment, utilizing technical skills and creativity to deliver visually appealing content.
- Successfully executed engaging social media campaigns to enhance the company's online presence.

# OFFICE ADMINISTRATION SF Lab on Wheels, Santa Maria Bulacan

11/2021 - 03/2022

- Proficient Company Administrator with expertise in Digital Marketing and Web Development.
- Played a crucial role in efficiently managing and coordinating clinic operations.
- Responsibilities included supervising client result certificates, scheduling home service clinics, preparing lab kits, and maintaining the company's online presence.
- Managed and optimized the company's Facebook page and website.
- Demonstrated exceptional organizational skills, meticulous attention to detail, and a strong commitment to delivering exceptional customer service in this multifaceted role.

### **SKILLS**

JAVASCRIPT • HTML • CSS • REACT • BOOTSTRAP • TAILWIND • ASP.NET • MSSQL • WEB DEVELOPMENT • EMBEDDED SYSTEM • COMPUTER ENGINEERING • COMPUTER HARDWARE • COMPUTER SOFTWARE • COMPUTER REPAIR • NETWORK ADMINISTRATION • UI DESIGN • UX DESIGN • WEB DESIGN • COMPUTER LITERACY • MICROSOFT OFFICE • ADOBE PHOTOSHOP • GRAPHIC DESIGN • LAYOUT DESIGN

#### **EDUCATION**

## BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN COMPUTER ENGINEERING 2019 - 2023

POLYTECHNIC UNIVERSITY OF THE PHILIPPINES

# SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGY, ENGINEERING, AND MATHEMATICS 2017 - 2019

SACRED HEART ACADEMY OF STA. MARIA INC.

### JUNIOR HIGHSCHOOL 2013 - 2017

GRACE OF SHEKINAH SCHOOL - SANTA MARIA

## **ELEMENTARY** 2007 - 2013

SAN GABRIEL ELEMENTARY SCHOOL

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

- Certification of Eligibility, Civil Service Commission 2023
- BSA-102 BrightSign Player and Network Setup, BrightSign 2023
- BSA-101 Welcome to BrightSign, BrightSign 2023
- Fixed Broadband Network, PUPSMB 2023
- MICROELECTRONICS: Introduction to Arduino, BatStateU-ARASOF
   2021